The planet rocks its cradle, dreaming a beautiful dream​
hoshi ga yuraide yume o miteiru​
As the voice it wants to hear so bad bides its time​
kogareta sono oto ga matteru no​
To days full of colors shining oh so vividly​
kirameku karaa himeteru hibi ni​
I dedicate this here melody​
tsutaeru kono merodi​
Hoshimachi Suisei - NEXT COLOR PLANET​
Lyrics: Hoshimachi Suisei​
Composition, Arrangement: Takuya Sakai (Arte Refact)​
I spy through the window glass​
mado kara nozoita ame no furu machinami o​
The pelting rain drench the city whole​
So let's take that popping sound in​
hajikeru oto dakara poketto ni tsumekonde Let's dance now​
Put it in our pockets, and let's dance now​
Your most favorite tune​
kimi no sukina​
(That li'l cool'n'pop party song)​
(chotto cool de pop na party song)​
I go groovin' in step with its killer beat​
kiraachuun no suteppu ni nosete​
(chotto cool de pop na party song)​
The magical spotlight​
mahou no you na​
(The very vivid, passionate, and shiny ray)​
(motto vivid, passion, shiny ray)​
Shines on me, glowing in a most brilliant hue​
raito ga watashi o terashiteru​
The planet tells its story, painting a beautiful dream​
hoshi o tsumuide yume o egaku yo​
As the voice it wants to hear so bad calls its name​
kogareta sono koe ga yonderu no​
To you, decked in colors shining oh so vividly​
kirameku karaa matotta kimi ni​
I dedicate this here melody​
todokeru kono merodi​
I can't fade away like this, not this way​
kono mama ja ne owarenai​
(No, not this way)​
(owaranai)​
This special ol' stage is my own dance floor​
Special na Sta​ge odoriakasu no​
(Let it flow)​
(akasou)​
I won't waste away like this, not today​
kono mama jitto shiterarenai​
(No, not this day)​
(sou sasenai)​
It is time to make a move, 'cause tomorrow the skies will clear​
hashiridasou yo ashita wa hareru kara​
The morning haze my eyes can't clear​
mada me ga samenai kaaten o hiraite mo​
Drawing the curtains is not helping, no​
Even if the gloom sets in​
yuuutsusou datte kometto ga nagaretara Let's show now​
Spot that comet in the sky, and it's showtime​
My favorite outfit​
itsumo kiteta​
(That li'l trendy'n'girly style)​
(chotto trend base na girly style)​
I change into that show-window display piece​
shouwindou no fuku kigaete​
(chotto trend base na girly style)​
In the magical moment​
mahou no you na​
(The very cool'n'pop party time)​
(motto cool de pop na party time)​
My lovely dress flutters in the air all for you​
doresu ga fuwari tte hirugaeru​
Look up at the starry sky above you​
manten no hoshizora ni hora ukabetemite asu no bijon​
And try to imagine your future vision​
If you can see it all, if you can see it all up there​
soko de mieru soko de mieru nara​
You can soar much higher​
motto toberu yo​
If your smile is in its full bloom​
mankai no egao nara hora utattemite kono tokimeki​
Go on and sing your racing heart out​
We will meet again, we will meet again right there​
soko de aeru soko de aeru kara​
'cause I'm sure tomorrow the world will change​
datte kitto sekai wa kawaru kara!​
'cause tomorrow the skies will clear​
ashita wa hareru kara​
The planet tells its story, painting a beautiful dream​
hoshi o tsumuide yume o egaku yo​
As the voice it wants to hear so bad calls its name​
kogareta sono koe ga yonderu no​
To you, decked in colors shining oh so vividly​
kirameku karaa matotta kimi ni​
I dedicate this here melody​
todokeru kono merodi​
I can't fade away like this, not this way​
kono mama ja ne owarenai​
(No, not this way)​
(owaranai)​
This special ol' stage is my own dance floor​
Special na Sta​ge odoriakasu no​
(Let it flow)​
(akasou)​
I won't waste away like this, not today​
kono mama jitto shiterarenai​
(No, not this day)​
(sou sasenai)​
It is time to make a move, 'cause tomorrow the world will change​
hashiridasou yo sekai wa kawaru kara​
(LaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLa)​
(LaLaLaLaLa)​
'cause tomorrow the skies will clear​
ashita wa hareru kara​
(LaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLa)​
LaLaLaLaLaLa​
(LaLaLaLaLa)​
'cause tomorrow we will meet again​
ashita mo aeru kara!​