Feeling like I'm almost dead, but I'm not
Oto mo nai kaze ni tadayou Bones
Togirete kienai koe no oto
Nanimo shiranai mama modorenai deshou
Onaji iro no me ni utsuru
Chigau iro no iki wo haku
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
Ushinau mono wa mou nanimo nai
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
No, I don't want it
I don't want it
But I know no one's there
Hazama wo tadotte
Feel like I'm living in your shadow
Asai kizu ni sumitsuita sorrows
Furiosenai sabita knife
Daremo shiranai kimi ga soko ni itan deshou
Dakishimete ageru yo
Sono iki wo sutte oyogu
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
Ashiba mo nai kotae mae e mukau
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
No, I don't want it
I don't want it
But I know no one's there
I know no one's there
I'll stay, I'll stay
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
Ushinau mono wa mou nanimo nai
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
No, I don't want it
I don't want it
Don't let me go (Don't let me go)
You're gonna make me drown (Don't let me go)
Ashiba mo nai kotae mae e mukau
You're gonna make me go
You're gonna make me drown
No, I don't want it
I don't want it
But I know no one's there
Ahh ah ah ah ah