Shallys
Contas hale’ilia on shallys
I journey ahead, holding on to my lantern
Ani mita potima i ji’ulyc
All the while thinking of the oasis
Zi clocs ocnoclez dinau keytyn
That’s right, I have many guardians watching over me
Hap’a myukil sha lu be’iru
This fortune will surely ring the bell of my hometown
Yaididila leu minas sak’chwa
The Princess will protect the sanctuary from evil
Dig nau e minas ligadia
The King will be the sword to cut off its hand
Dishi di lasweina veticas
Blessings upon the future of the girl who’d set off again
Di mi woilaj molof hap’a
even if swallowed in the vortex of a foreign world
Contas hale’ilia on shallys
I journey ahead, holding on to my lantern
Ani mita potima i ji’ulyc
All the while thinking of the oasis
Aloviatolum stulia
This is a story about a traveler
Non tocias stulia
And a story about none other than you
Contas hale’ilia on shallys
I journey ahead, holding on to my lantern
Ani mita potima i ji’ulyc
All the while thinking of the oasis
Zi clocs ocnoclez dinau keytyn
That’s right, I have many guardians watching over me
Hap’a myukil sha lu be’iru
This fortune will surely ring the bell of my hometown
Es tuna ligali vidia
If you have a duty to fulfill, you must live on
Falatost lumia diz lomo
Death may be honorable, but virtuous it is not
Kuls winia nina i ji’ulyc
Raise your voice, raise your fist, raise your lantern
Menelasm oclulu
Lift your head and remember your bonds of trust
Dililalu pipuru nodomuru
Step after step I grow more certain
Fal’ma invilale mam sillifri
And spurred on by the fal’ma crying out to me,
Onomabul vaniro undal’ne
I run my fingers through the stream and send my words drifting off
Dina wia salame
Now then, let’s sing in place of the monument—
Te cant milalila ah
the song of this land that stretches out however far
Hafit lasimiya
When I stand still and look to the sky,
Fimola shelo niconia
I see the faces of my beloved family
Dimi woi plop’po neona
And when I set off again and look to my side,
Fimola shelo lala...
I see the faces of my beloved friends...
Contas hale’ilia on shallys
I journey ahead, holding on to my lantern
Ani mita potima i ji’ulyc
All the while thinking of the oasis
Zi clocs ocnoclez dinau keytyn
That’s right, I have many guardians watching over me
Hap’a myukil sha lu be’iru
This fortune will surely ring the bell of my hometown
Mo lyu pe sant
Don’t worry, for yesterday’s wounds have already healed
Mo lata te cant
Don’t worry, for today like before, the land is on your side
Di mi woilaj molof hola...
Please, bring blessings upon the girl’s future...
Di mi woilaj molof hap’a
Blessings upon her future as she sets off again