kazesasou kokage ni utsubusete naiteru​
Shaded by the trees, calling out to the wind, I'm lying face-down crying
mi mo shiranu watashi wo watashi ga miteita​
I saw a version of myself I didn't even recognize
yuku hito no shirabe wo kanaderu gitaara​
On this guitar I'm playing the melody of someone who's passed on
konu hito no nageki ni hoshi wa ochite​
A star falls in the grief of someone who'll never be seen again
yukanaide, donna ni sakende mo​
Please don't go, no matter how much you scream,
orenji no hanabira shizuka ni yureru dake​
all it will do is quietly stir these orange petals
yawarakana hitai ni nokosareta​
Saved on my soft brow,
te no hira no kioku haruka​
I send the memories in my palm far away
tokoshie no sayonara tsuma hiku​
An eternal farewell as I keep strumming
"The Wheel of Dawn" - FictionJunction YUUKA​
Lyrics: Kajiura Yuki​
Music: Kajiura Yuki​
Covered by Tokino Sora​ and AZKi
yasashii te ni sugaru kodomo no kokoro wo​
The heart of a child clinging to a gentle hand
moesakaru kuruma wa furiharai susumu​
The blazing wheels cast it off and continue on
yuku hito no nageki wo kanadete gitaara​
On this guitar I'm playing the grief of someone who's passed on
mune no ito hageshiku kakinarashite​
The strings in my heart being plucked at violently
aa kanashimi ni somaranai shirosa de​
In the pure white unstained by sorrow,
orenji no hanabira yureteta natsu no kage ni​
the orange petals stirred in a summer shadow
yawarakana hitai wo nakushite mo​
Even if my soft brow is lost,
akaku someta suna haruka koete iku​
I'll cross over the far off, red-stained sand
sayonara no rizumu​
The rhythm of farewell
omoide wo yakitsukushite susumu daichi ni​
Branded into my memories, on the ever-turning earth,
natsukashiku me fuite iku mono ga aru no​
there is something sprouting in remembrance
akatsuki no kuruma wo miokutte​
Sending off the dawn's carriage
orenji no hanabira yureteru ima mo dokoka​
Those orange petals are stirring somewhere even now
itsuka mita yasurakana yoake wo​
The peaceful daybreak I once saw
mou ichido te ni suru made​
Until it is placed in my hands once more,
kesanaide tomoshibi​
please don't let the light go out
kuruma wa mawaru yo​
The wheels are turning