I'm neither an angel or a devil
Our hearts are just some broken refletion in someone else's mirror
Choosing between options A and B
is according to the attitude of you who always walk on my right side
I like the darkening blue of the skies after school
I can't feel anything in a frenetic classoom
In an angle that teachers can't see, somewhere parents don't know about,
my heart is well hidden
Good kids all start going home
Black crows start cawing
My reflection in you
is a pure resonance trusts in people's hearts
The reason I don't say goodbye is because
I don't want to be penetrated by you
Es...
The kids who only pretend to be earnest in front of teachers fill me with disgust
As I said so, you hanged your head in sadness
Actually I don't really care about this, the main subject is something else
The badness is well hidden
Good kids all grow into adults,
wake up from their dreams
The memories of walking alongside you
and your back with sagacity started to fade
The reason I don't say thank you is because
I don't want to have any chance to be disliked by you
I am aware of all of my flaws
The shadow strikes first
Every time on our way home,
I become fragile as I drift away from you
The reason I don't say goodbye is because
I don't want you to be swallowed by the loneliness
The neglected third heart had been
staring at the two of us